{
    "subject": "resource/184th_Pennsylvania_Infantry",
    "predicate": "ontology/battle",
    "object": "resource/Siege_of_Petersburg",
    "human_readable": "The 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was involved in the Siege of Petersburg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.987076461315155,
            "question": "What significant role did the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry play during the Siege of Petersburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9624112248420715,
            "question": "Name a battle that the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was involved in."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8335102200508118,
            "question": "Which historical event did the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry take part in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6904372572898865,
            "question": "Who were the opposing forces involved in the Siege of Petersburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6373699307441711,
            "question": "Where did the Siege of Petersburg take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6334642171859741,
            "question": "What military unit participated in the Siege of Petersburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6242480874061584,
            "question": "During which war or conflict was the Siege of Petersburg fought?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5872783064842224,
            "question": "What type of military engagement was the Siege of Petersburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3450409471988678,
            "question": "What were some of the key outcomes of the Siege of Petersburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.256013959646225,
            "question": "How long did the Siege of Petersburg last?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was involved in the Siege of Petersburg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3046_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the key outcomes of the Siege of Petersburg?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3046_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of military engagement was the Siege of Petersburg?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3046_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=During which war or conflict was the Siege of Petersburg fought?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3046_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3046_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3046_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3046_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3046_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3046_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3046_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3046_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3046_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3046_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3046_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was involved in the Siege of Petersburg. This can be inferred from the dates and events mentioned, such as \"Siege of Petersburg June 16, 1864, to April 2, 1865,\" which indicates their participation in this significant military campaign."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}